

5104 Proper Tunghaan Minglanilla, Cebu 6046 ADDRESS

(+63) 943 221 9155 PHONE

johnlloydmayol@gmail.com E-MAIL

https://github.com/mayol27

www.linkedin.com/in/johnlloyd-mayol

ABOUT ME

A skilled IT affluent young professional with more than 4 years of experience Software Development & Design, Hardware and Software Maintenance and Repair, and Graphics Design enhancing PHP in Languages Programming (Laravel, Codeigniter, CSS, Bootstrap, W3, CSS, and HTML).

SKILLS

WORK

PHOTOSHOP

ILLUSTRATOR

LARAVEL

CODEIGNITER

PHP

MYSQL

HTML

CSS

JOHN LLOYD SEGISMAR MAYOL

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

EXPERIENCE

(October 2019)

Devcash

THESIS

A SOFTWARE-AS-A-SERVICE FOR CASHIERING SYSTEM FOR MICRO AND SMALL ENTERPRISES

Position: Hipster

Language: Angular.js, PHP, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, Android, and Firebase (June 2015 – October 2019)

WORKING SCHOLAR – UNIVERSITY OF CEBU

LABORATORY ASSISTANT

- + Technical support for hardware and software
- + Assisting students and teachers on computer laboratory
- + Sorting and filing documents

(October 2018 - May 2019)

ON-THE JOB TRAINIG - KREDO IT ABROD INC.

PROGRAMMER

- + Technical support for hardware and software
- + Created Inventory System for the company

EDUCATION

(June 2015 - October 2019)

University of Cebu – Main Campus

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

(June 2011 - March 2015)

Immaculate Heart of Mary Academy – Minglanilla HIGH SCHOOL

ORGANIZATION

(March 2017 – Present)

GDG Cebu - Google Developers Group

(April 2015 – October 2019)

UNIVERSITY OF CEBU – ASSOCIATION OF WORKING SCHOLARS (AWS)

(June 2015 – October 2019)

UNIVERSITY OF CEBU – PHILIPPINE SOCIETY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY STUDENT (PSITS)

CERTIFICATES

(2018)

Building Entrepreneurial Ecosystem to Enhance Higher Education Value-Added for Better Graduate Employability (BEEHIVE) – MOOC

(2017)

5th UC-ICT Congress "Sharpening Junior Mobile Technologists"

(2016)

4th UC-ICT Congress "Shaping up Creative Minds through Great UX Design"

BOOTSTRAP
C
C++
TROUBLESHOOT

Ms. Ma. Catherine Carumba

Secretary – College of Computer Studies

Contact: 255 – 7777 loc. 113

PERSONAL

COMMUNICATION

ORGANIZATION

TEAM PLAYER

CREATIVITY

SOCIAL

Ms. Lina J. Perez

UCEMPC – Secretary Contact: 255 – 7777 loc. 136 Ms. Jerrah Marie Son

REFERENCE

Laboratory Supervisor – CCS

Contact: 0923 – 866 – 7880